/* 1 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603643890c817f0398fa436f"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-business-analyst-a-good-job?-",
    "answer" : "Hemang Sharma Business Analytics is indeed one of the hottest skills in the job market today - top recruiters from different industries are preferring technically skilled professionals now, more than ever. Data and business intelligence is already reshaping business as we know it, and might just be able to minimize human errors and predictable issues beforehand. Now, coming to your question - it is hard to put together what you mean by ‘good’. If we try and talk from an industry perspective, a good job should be able to provide you with ease of work, high demand among recruiters, good compensation package, growth in the future, and of course, job satisfaction. Now let us see how the Business Analyst job role fairs in these parameters - High demand - Yes, the skill is one of the preferred skills when it co Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:16:09.373Z"),
    "question" : "Is business analyst a good job? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036438d0c817f0398fa43a9"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-responsibilities-of-a-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Ashok Vardhan Sanda I am completing 3 years working in Business Analytics in a week, so I would love to shed some light on what we mythical creatures do. First a little bit of background to set the mood. I graduated from NIT-Silchar in 2013 as a Electrical Engineering major. As there was a dearth of core jobs(jobs which requires a person to use the concept learnt during college), I decided to go with the offer I had in hand from my campus placement in Mu Sigma, Bangalore . In the first 25 days of joining the company we were expected to learn the following subjects(at least the basics) SQL, 2. Excel, 3. SaS, 4. R-programming, 5. Statistical ConceptsAlong with those 5 subjects we were divided into the groups of 2s and 3s to work on a project which was already done by teams in past. For me the project was to figu Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:16:13.176Z"),
    "question" : "What are the responsibilities of a business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 3 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036439e0c817f0398fa43ce"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-start-a-career-as-a-Business-Analyst-with-no-experience?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How do I start a career as a Business Analyst with no experience?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:16:30.798Z"),
    "question" : "How do I start a career as a Business Analyst with no experience? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 4 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603643b70c817f0398fa43e8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-career-path-for-a-Business-Analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Business Analyst Career Progression We will first explore the foundational knowledge and skills needed in the early part of a business analysts' career and then what is required to progress. Entry-level Business Analyst From a foundational knowledge perspective, the first thing a BA must possess is some technical aptitude. This does not mean a BA has to have a degree in Management Information Systems, or Software Engineering but they do have to understand what a software application is and how it works i.e. processes translate to logic, data is information the business cares about, business rules govern the way a business operates. The reason this knowledge is important is because most BA's will start their careers at the project level working on software enhancements and implementations. In  Continue Reading Business Analyst Career Progression We will first explore the foundational knowledge and skills needed in the early part of a business analysts' career and then what is required to progress. Entry-level Business Analyst From a foundational knowledge perspective, the first thing a BA must possess is some technical aptitude. This does not mean a BA has to have a degree in Management Information Systems, or Software Engineering but they do have to understand what a software application is and how it works i.e. processes translate to logic, data is information the business cares about, business rules govern the way a business operates. The reason this knowledge is important is because most BA's will start their careers at the project level working on software enhancements and implementations. In  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:16:55.231Z"),
    "question" : "What is the career path for a Business Analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 5 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603643ca0c817f0398fa4430"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-scope-of-career-as-a-business-analyst-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Business analysts are responsible for mending the gap between the IT and the business using business analytics tools to evaluate the processes, discover the requirements, and providing data-driven reports and suggestions to the executives and stakeholders. It is a practice of enabling transformation on the context of the organization by the definite solutions to bring value and help them to reach the organizational goal. The International Institute of Business Analysis (IIBA), a non-profit professional association, contemplates the business analysts as an agent of change and business analysis is the disciplined approach for providing changes to the organization so they can bring profit to businesses and governments. A business analyst in present time does multitasking; as per the requirement Continue Reading Business analysts are responsible for mending the gap between the IT and the business using business analytics tools to evaluate the processes, discover the requirements, and providing data-driven reports and suggestions to the executives and stakeholders. It is a practice of enabling transformation on the context of the organization by the definite solutions to bring value and help them to reach the organizational goal. The International Institute of Business Analysis (IIBA), a non-profit professional association, contemplates the business analysts as an agent of change and business analysis is the disciplined approach for providing changes to the organization so they can bring profit to businesses and governments. A business analyst in present time does multitasking; as per the requirement Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:17:14.406Z"),
    "question" : "What is the scope of career as a business analyst in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 6 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603643de0c817f0398fa4444"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-Business-analyst-a-dying-career?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Is Business analyst a dying career?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:17:34.330Z"),
    "question" : "Is Business analyst a dying career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 7 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603643f00c817f0398fa445c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-ways-to-prepare-to-become-a-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "LN Mishra According to IIBA’s Business Analysis Body of Knowledge v3.0 (BABoK®), business analysis is the practice of enabling change in an enterprise by defining needs and recommending solutions that deliver value to stakeholders. Business analysts, therefore, understand the problems and goals of an enterprise, analyze needs and solution, devise change strategies, drive change, collaborate with stakeholders and also advise organizations on improving efficiency, finances, and various other aspects of the business. The question implies that you either want to switch over to a Business Analysis career or want to start your professional career as a Business Analyst. The best ways to prepare to become a business analyst are: · While entering the field of business analysis, a broad understanding of business Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:17:52.317Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best ways to prepare to become a business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 8 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603644040c817f0398fa44a1"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-career-growth-if-I-start-as-a-business-analyst-today?-",
    "answer" : "There are many paths that can come out of starting as a BA, and that is why for me it is a fantastic choice for many that are trying to determine exactly where they want to go while having an interest and talent for solving problems.  Instead of \"career growth\" think of it more as \"tools in your toolbox\".  In most organizations a BA would need to work with development teams, customer facing teams, project management teams, their own BA team, and potentially executive management.  That is an immense amount of exposure (in a good way) to the key stakeholders in any organization.  Learning how to organize and analyze data, articulate solutions and recommendations in writing, and then give a presentation on those findings are also very likely scenarios within a year of starting.   If done well  Continue Reading There are many paths that can come out of starting as a BA, and that is why for me it is a fantastic choice for many that are trying to determine exactly where they want to go while having an interest and talent for solving problems.  Instead of \"career growth\" think of it more as \"tools in your toolbox\".  In most organizations a BA would need to work with development teams, customer facing teams, project management teams, their own BA team, and potentially executive management.  That is an immense amount of exposure (in a good way) to the key stakeholders in any organization.  Learning how to organize and analyze data, articulate solutions and recommendations in writing, and then give a presentation on those findings are also very likely scenarios within a year of starting.   If done well  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:18:12.033Z"),
    "question" : "What is the career growth if I start as a business analyst today? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 9 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603644170c817f0398fa44b9"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-it-like-to-be-a-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "It is very hard to be a business analyst. The skills required can range from customer meetings getting requirements and working with customer staff. I have found that a analyst has to know the business of a client and have business knowledge. Most of the work is learning each job that is done in the business and the information required by the job. I would say it is very much like building a machine that you can not see and the parts that my not be working. It is the one job where the analyst is required to insure that all the parts are known and will do the job. I have only see a few people in my 40 years who had the skills to design and install software.. This is a skill you can not teach someone, they need to have a full range of skills. When I was doing this job, I had to keep my design i Continue Reading It is very hard to be a business analyst. The skills required can range from customer meetings getting requirements and working with customer staff. I have found that a analyst has to know the business of a client and have business knowledge. Most of the work is learning each job that is done in the business and the information required by the job. I would say it is very much like building a machine that you can not see and the parts that my not be working. It is the one job where the analyst is required to insure that all the parts are known and will do the job. I have only see a few people in my 40 years who had the skills to design and install software.. This is a skill you can not teach someone, they need to have a full range of skills. When I was doing this job, I had to keep my design i Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:18:31.820Z"),
    "question" : "What is it like to be a business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 10 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036442e0c817f0398fa44d4"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-business-analyst-certification?-",
    "answer" : "There is just one certification related to Business Analyst role which is highly regarded world-wide. And that’s CBAP. And no other certification (literally no other) worth spending money upon. Most of the companies don’t bother if you are a ECBA, CCBA or any other certified professional. What interviewers question you would be based on project based scenarios which can be answered better based on practical knowledge. Certifications should generally help in either gaining brownie points during interviews or should help in learning more about the specific tool or language or field. I doubt if either of these purposes are met by a non-CBAP certification for a BA. Pre-requisite for a CBAP is that the person should have spent around 5 years as a Business Analyst. Along with other few conditions Continue Reading There is just one certification related to Business Analyst role which is highly regarded world-wide. And that’s CBAP. And no other certification (literally no other) worth spending money upon. Most of the companies don’t bother if you are a ECBA, CCBA or any other certified professional. What interviewers question you would be based on project based scenarios which can be answered better based on practical knowledge. Certifications should generally help in either gaining brownie points during interviews or should help in learning more about the specific tool or language or field. I doubt if either of these purposes are met by a non-CBAP certification for a BA. Pre-requisite for a CBAP is that the person should have spent around 5 years as a Business Analyst. Along with other few conditions Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:18:54.647Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best business analyst certification? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 11 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036443f0c817f0398fa4514"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-did-you-start-your-career-as-a-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Well my journey of becoming a Business Analyst have been an interesting roller coaster ride. After completing my engineering, I was very skeptical about how my career will proceed. Then I got campus placement in a big MNC. I was happy that at least I got placement. But then the training time and coding practices became a nightmare for me. I was barely able to pass the training time. Then I expected that I will get allocation in a QA department or Production Support department, where coding will not be a worry for me. But I got allocation in software development team that was responsible for coding in Java, JSP, JS and what not. So my nightmare got more horrific. But gradually as I became more aware about the process of development, I got knowledge about Business Analyst job profile. I found  Continue Reading Well my journey of becoming a Business Analyst have been an interesting roller coaster ride. After completing my engineering, I was very skeptical about how my career will proceed. Then I got campus placement in a big MNC. I was happy that at least I got placement. But then the training time and coding practices became a nightmare for me. I was barely able to pass the training time. Then I expected that I will get allocation in a QA department or Production Support department, where coding will not be a worry for me. But I got allocation in software development team that was responsible for coding in Java, JSP, JS and what not. So my nightmare got more horrific. But gradually as I became more aware about the process of development, I got knowledge about Business Analyst job profile. I found  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:19:11.668Z"),
    "question" : "How did you start your career as a business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 12 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603644550c817f0398fa452e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-a-data-analyst-and-a-data-scientist?-",
    "answer" : "Data analyst is anyone who works with data to derive actionable insights. Overall trend is moving towards using data scientist term more than data analysts for such professional. Some companies don’t differentiate between a data scientist and analytics professional (or data analysts) and use these terms interchangeably to define their team members. On the other hand, significant number of companies do have this differentiation. In general, here are the factors that in my opinion can separate the two.  However for being successful either as a Data Scientist or Business Analytics Or Data Analyst professional, following are the must have skills- Love for numbers and quantitative stuffGrit to keep on learningLove for coding and programmingStructured thinking approachPassion for solving problemsGood Continue Reading Data analyst is anyone who works with data to derive actionable insights. Overall trend is moving towards using data scientist term more than data analysts for such professional. Some companies don’t differentiate between a data scientist and analytics professional (or data analysts) and use these terms interchangeably to define their team members. On the other hand, significant number of companies do have this differentiation. In general, here are the factors that in my opinion can separate the two.  However for being successful either as a Data Scientist or Business Analytics Or Data Analyst professional, following are the must have skills- Love for numbers and quantitative stuffGrit to keep on learningLove for coding and programmingStructured thinking approachPassion for solving problemsGood Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:19:33.916Z"),
    "question" : "What is the difference between a data analyst and a data scientist? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036448a0c817f0398fa459c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-additional-certification-should-I-take-as-a-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Iresh Rie Dacian I assumed that you’re considering a career shift? I based this observation based on your question. Summary: You can become Business Analyst without certifications. It’s not necessary that you have the Business Analyst title to be considered as BA as long as you do what a BA usually do. To become globally recognized, there are available certifications but usually requires the all important experience. IT will also strengthen your foundation and be familiar to acceptable jargon of the field. Relevant Business Analysis Certifications requires experience. But here is one Level 1 - ECBA - IIBA that might help you. That’s the only one that I’ve encountered that is globally recognized. This one will give you a skeleton of what BA usually do. Now, I want you to focus on your experience. Many people w Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:20:26.379Z"),
    "question" : "What additional certification should I take as a business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 14 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036449c0c817f0398fa45ac"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-become-a-business-analyst-as-a-fresher?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How do I become a business analyst as a fresher?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:20:44.772Z"),
    "question" : "How do I become a business analyst as a fresher? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 15 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603644af0c817f0398fa45c4"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-scope-of-business-analysts-in-the-near-future?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the scope of business analysts in the near future?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:21:03.373Z"),
    "question" : "What is the scope of business analysts in the near future? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 16 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603644c30c817f0398fa4612"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-an-engineering-graduate-pursue-his-career-as-a-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Why Not..? Necessary Business Analyst Skills:- Communication SkillsBy nature of the job, business analysts spend a great deal of time interacting with users, clients, management and developers. A project’s success may depend upon the business analyst clearly communicating details like project requirements, requested changes and testing results. Fluent language skills and written communication abilities are necessary to thrive in a business analyst career.Technical SkillsIn order to identify business solutions, a business analyst should know what information technology applications are being utilized, what new possible outcomes can be achieved through current platforms and what the latest technology offers. Testing software and designing business systems are also important technical businesContinue Reading Why Not..? Necessary Business Analyst Skills:- Communication SkillsBy nature of the job, business analysts spend a great deal of time interacting with users, clients, management and developers. A project’s success may depend upon the business analyst clearly communicating details like project requirements, requested changes and testing results. Fluent language skills and written communication abilities are necessary to thrive in a business analyst career.Technical SkillsIn order to identify business solutions, a business analyst should know what information technology applications are being utilized, what new possible outcomes can be achieved through current platforms and what the latest technology offers. Testing software and designing business systems are also important technical businesContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:21:23.211Z"),
    "question" : "Can an engineering graduate pursue his career as a business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 17 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603644d60c817f0398fa461c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-should-be-the-career-goals-of-a-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Before applying for any job, it is necessary to be sure of the professional goals so that a balance can be maintained in the job catering and position advancement. There are several goals both technical and non-technical that must be kept in mind while working as a business analyst or before stepping into the shoes of a business analyst. Given below are some of the important goals that should be adhered to by every individual in the field of business analysis. Analytical and technical skills While working on an analytics project it is necessary to have an individual in the team who knows the technical stuff such as databases(SQL, Oracle, etc.) or a person who is well equipped with business software such as visualization tools, programming languages like R, Python, etc. Apart from these techn Continue Reading Before applying for any job, it is necessary to be sure of the professional goals so that a balance can be maintained in the job catering and position advancement. There are several goals both technical and non-technical that must be kept in mind while working as a business analyst or before stepping into the shoes of a business analyst. Given below are some of the important goals that should be adhered to by every individual in the field of business analysis. Analytical and technical skills While working on an analytics project it is necessary to have an individual in the team who knows the technical stuff such as databases(SQL, Oracle, etc.) or a person who is well equipped with business software such as visualization tools, programming languages like R, Python, etc. Apart from these techn Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:21:42.647Z"),
    "question" : "What should be the career goals of a business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 18 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603644e90c817f0398fa4638"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-change-my-job-from-being-a-software-developer-to-a-business-analyst?-I-want-to-interact-with-people-more-and-solve-real-business-problems.-",
    "answer" : "Here is my piece of advice: Contact/Network with people known to you, currently working as BA. Ask for their reference/recommendation. I wouldn’t recommend just applying using hiring portals etc. as they have limited credibility. You might just not get reply from these companies.Head on to Linkedin and look for people who are already working with the profile that you desire. It might be a good idea to check their skills and consecutively building them while working at your current company.Lastly, try getting some real experience. Look for small~medium sized companies which hire both BA and software engineers. Try switching to these companies and getting some experience that would suffice for your transition into BA profile. This would also give you the opportunity to interact with the emploContinue Reading Here is my piece of advice: Contact/Network with people known to you, currently working as BA. Ask for their reference/recommendation. I wouldn’t recommend just applying using hiring portals etc. as they have limited credibility. You might just not get reply from these companies.Head on to Linkedin and look for people who are already working with the profile that you desire. It might be a good idea to check their skills and consecutively building them while working at your current company.Lastly, try getting some real experience. Look for small~medium sized companies which hire both BA and software engineers. Try switching to these companies and getting some experience that would suffice for your transition into BA profile. This would also give you the opportunity to interact with the emploContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:22:01.276Z"),
    "question" : "How do I change my job from being a software developer to a business analyst? I want to interact with people more and solve real business problems. ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 19 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603644fb0c817f0398fa4681"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-a-business-analyst-a-dead-end-career?-",
    "answer" : "Not at all, it's quite opposite of that. I hope you read a similar question answer I had written a few days ago. Sagar Joshi's answer to Is Business analyst a dying career? Just like every company needs a salesperson the same way most of the IT companies need a BA. In simple terms, ​a Business Analyst is a bridge between the customer and the project team. So as there is huge boom in the IT industry and the future is IT only, the demand is sure to increase. I hope this will help :) Adam Haesler",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:22:19.439Z"),
    "question" : "Is a business analyst a dead end career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 20 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603645330c817f0398fa46e7"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-job-opportunities-for-the-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are the job opportunities for the business analyst?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:23:15.777Z"),
    "question" : "What are the job opportunities for the business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 21 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603645440c817f0398fa46fc"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-much-of-programming-is-needed-for-a-career-as-a-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Thanks for A2A  For those who know programming well, I can say they are into Business System Analyst not Business Analyst. They have the upper edge for sure. As a business analyst your job role would be only around the requirement gathering, documentation, testing etc. But if you want to move a step ahead then you can assist developer with their programming part because you know the code and may predict the behavior also. Another thing, you can handle client more clearly with the programming issue. Most of the clients are non-programming background, but if they know about coding or you are dealing with CTO then you need to know about the coding.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:23:32.395Z"),
    "question" : "How much of programming is needed for a career as a business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 22 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603645550c817f0398fa470c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-exactly-does-a-business-analyst-do?-What-are-the-skill-sets-required-from-an-undergrad-who-wants-to-pursue-a-career-as-a-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:23:49.324Z"),
    "question" : "How do you differentiate from others in the business analyst role? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 23 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036457d0c817f0398fa476c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-switch-my-career-from-sales-to-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How do I switch my career from sales to business analyst?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:24:29.052Z"),
    "question" : "How do I switch my career from sales to business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 24 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036458e0c817f0398fa4778"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-transition-from-a-developer-to-a-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "I was a developer before I moved to being Business Analyst. Here are my tips if you are looking to become a Functional Business Analyst. 1. How can one's programming skills be used as an advantage in being a business analyst? Business analyst acts as a bridge between a development team and the client. Since you know what a developer expects while developing, you will be able to interview the client better and answer your team better.You would be able to think how a requirement would translate into a program, what is a better solution etc. You will be able to analyze some situations better without always consulting a developer. You will be able to give better estimates for ball park release dates.Hence it's always an advantage being a business analyst who knows programming. 2. What prompt Continue Reading I was a developer before I moved to being Business Analyst. Here are my tips if you are looking to become a Functional Business Analyst. 1. How can one's programming skills be used as an advantage in being a business analyst? Business analyst acts as a bridge between a development team and the client. Since you know what a developer expects while developing, you will be able to interview the client better and answer your team better.You would be able to think how a requirement would translate into a program, what is a better solution etc. You will be able to analyze some situations better without always consulting a developer. You will be able to give better estimates for ball park release dates.Hence it's always an advantage being a business analyst who knows programming. 2. What prompt Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:24:46.673Z"),
    "question" : "How do I transition from a developer to a business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 25 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603645c30c817f0398fa47eb"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-difficult-it-is-to-pursue-a-career-in-Business-Analytics-without-having-a-prior-experience-as-an-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Software testing (manual or automated does not matter) in an Indian outsourcing firm is a blot which takes some time to erase. Also, the chance that you will get a analytics/big data/machine learning project in TCS is, of course, close to zero. So your only option is to move to another company. The problem though will be your background in testing and no relevant experience in analytics. As analytics is a very fast moving field with new frameworks being released on monthly basis and industry changing trend in a yearly basis (batch, streaming, lambda architecture, machine learning and now deep learning) it is very difficult to keep on top of the trend. Here is your opportunity - Try to do some courses on EdX and Coursera related to big data and machine learning - This will show your enthusiaContinue Reading Software testing (manual or automated does not matter) in an Indian outsourcing firm is a blot which takes some time to erase. Also, the chance that you will get a analytics/big data/machine learning project in TCS is, of course, close to zero. So your only option is to move to another company. The problem though will be your background in testing and no relevant experience in analytics. As analytics is a very fast moving field with new frameworks being released on monthly basis and industry changing trend in a yearly basis (batch, streaming, lambda architecture, machine learning and now deep learning) it is very difficult to keep on top of the trend. Here is your opportunity - Try to do some courses on EdX and Coursera related to big data and machine learning - This will show your enthusiaContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:25:39.826Z"),
    "question" : "How difficult it is to pursue a career in Business Analytics without having a prior experience as an analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 26 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603645ec0c817f0398fa4850"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-procedure-to-switch-from-a-developer-role-to-a-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the procedure to switch from a developer role to a business analyst?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:26:20.137Z"),
    "question" : "What is the procedure to switch from a developer role to a business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 27 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036460e0c817f0398fa4870"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-you-become-a-data-scientist-from-being-a-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Yes and no. A Data analyst should have a programming background and strong mathematical skills. Let just list down the skill sets of Data scientists. DATA SCIENTIST 25 Things You Need to Know About Data Science With over 6 billion (and counting) devices connected to the internet right now, as much as 2.5 million terabytes of data are generated every single day. By 2020, millions of more devices are expected to get connected, projecting an estimate of around 30 million terabytes of data every day. As a fresher or an IT professional, this should fascinate you. If you’ve been reading the news of late, I’m sure you’re aware of the massive layoffs across the tech companies in India. So, at this point in time, one thing that becomes essential is the need to re-skill to something more rewarding and au Continue Reading Yes and no. A Data analyst should have a programming background and strong mathematical skills. Let just list down the skill sets of Data scientists. DATA SCIENTIST 25 Things You Need to Know About Data Science With over 6 billion (and counting) devices connected to the internet right now, as much as 2.5 million terabytes of data are generated every single day. By 2020, millions of more devices are expected to get connected, projecting an estimate of around 30 million terabytes of data every day. As a fresher or an IT professional, this should fascinate you. If you’ve been reading the news of late, I’m sure you’re aware of the massive layoffs across the tech companies in India. So, at this point in time, one thing that becomes essential is the need to re-skill to something more rewarding and au Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:26:54.561Z"),
    "question" : "How do you become a data scientist from being a business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 28 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036461f0c817f0398fa48b4"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-mould-my-career-path-into-becoming-a-Product-Manager-from-a-Business-Analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Bryan McCarty When talking to others about how they became a PM, you will discover that each person's path is unique. We all take different routes to get here! After spending many years on product teams and having been a product manager myself, the best advice I can give is to find and work on products that you are passionate about. If your goal is simply to become a product manager, I think you are setting yourself up to fail. Instead, pick an industry that interest you and make it your goal to join a product team in that space. Even if you start out as a business analyst, you will be happier spending your time on something you care about, and it will show in your work. If you are already working in an industry of interest, you could spend your spare time building your own app or startup idea. Building you Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:27:11.750Z"),
    "question" : "How do I mould my career path into becoming a Product Manager from a Business Analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 29 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603646300c817f0398fa48c8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-a-business-analyst-a-better-career-option-than-SAP?-",
    "answer" : "Jessica Albert, phd Business Analysis & Quality Assurance, St. Louis, MOAnswered 2 years ago · Author has 157 answers and 391.5K answer viewsIs a business analyst a better career option than SAP? Jessica Albert As this is a career, this should be chosen by the individual based on their interest, As both business analyst and SAP are in the leading position and have a good career growth in this both field, there is huge openings and demands in this both fields, its you need to decide to which field you should opt for. Business Analyst is the person who analyses the organisation requirement business domain (real or hypothetical) and documents its business or processes or systems, assessing the business model or its integration with technology. Future scope of Business Analyst Roles and Responsibilities of Business Analyst Business Analyst Payscale SAP Consultant: SAP consultants are people who have understanding of this business and SAP ERP software, A functional consultant evaluates the demands in talki Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:27:28.513Z"),
    "question" : "Is a business analyst a better career option than SAP? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 30 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603646570c817f0398fa48ee"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-scope-and-future-growth-of-a-career-as-a-business-analyst-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Scope of being a business analyst is endless in India, Top tier firms like accenture, infosys, Wipro, IBM and TCS are using business analytics tools to generate business solutions to make larger profits. There are various private universities and colleges’ that offer full-time courses on business analysis, and if you are looking for specific job oriented programs, then there are many certification courses that are available in the market. Career Path: 1. Business Analyst or BA: Purely concentrating on being a business analyst can help you in many ways. Once you are thorough in being a BA, you can easily change or switch industries to find the one you are comfortable with or that suits you and start working at all levels of the company once you have enough experience. 2. Business Analysis Manag Continue Reading Scope of being a business analyst is endless in India, Top tier firms like accenture, infosys, Wipro, IBM and TCS are using business analytics tools to generate business solutions to make larger profits. There are various private universities and colleges’ that offer full-time courses on business analysis, and if you are looking for specific job oriented programs, then there are many certification courses that are available in the market. Career Path: 1. Business Analyst or BA: Purely concentrating on being a business analyst can help you in many ways. Once you are thorough in being a BA, you can easily change or switch industries to find the one you are comfortable with or that suits you and start working at all levels of the company once you have enough experience. 2. Business Analysis Manag Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:28:07.735Z"),
    "question" : "What is the scope and future growth of a career as a business analyst in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 31 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603646680c817f0398fa493c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-motivates-a-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Bill Dewitt  Vishak Subramanyan",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:28:24.539Z"),
    "question" : "What motivates a business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 32 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036467c0c817f0398fa4948"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-shift-my-career-to-a-business-analyst-role-from-IT-Programming?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How do I shift my career to a business analyst role from IT Programming?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:28:44.297Z"),
    "question" : "How do I shift my career to a business analyst role from IT Programming? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 33 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603646a10c817f0398fa49aa"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-change-my-career-from-business-development-to-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How do I change my career from business development to business analyst?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:29:21.815Z"),
    "question" : "How do I change my career from business development to business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 34 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603646c30c817f0398fa49ca"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-careers-offers-the-best-salary-Business-Analyst-or-QA-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "In the UK according CWjobs https://www.cwjobs.co.uk/salary-checker/average-business-analyst-salary Business Analysts attract a better salary than QA Analysts.   Though you shouldn’t choose a job based on the salary, after all there are better paying careers out there than both of these. The following from Alastair Majury on “What does being a BA mean to you?” may help you to decide if being a Business Analyst is an attractive proposition for you. I came across this thread on LinkedIn titled — “What does being a BA mean to you?”. The original post is: “What does being a BA mean to you? As someone very passionate about what I do, I will like to read and know how you feel being a BA (including Data, Systems, Infrastructure, … Analysts). Please share your thoughts.” And here are some of the responses: “I  Continue Reading In the UK according CWjobs https://www.cwjobs.co.uk/salary-checker/average-business-analyst-salary Business Analysts attract a better salary than QA Analysts.   Though you shouldn’t choose a job based on the salary, after all there are better paying careers out there than both of these. The following from Alastair Majury on “What does being a BA mean to you?” may help you to decide if being a Business Analyst is an attractive proposition for you. I came across this thread on LinkedIn titled — “What does being a BA mean to you?”. The original post is: “What does being a BA mean to you? As someone very passionate about what I do, I will like to read and know how you feel being a BA (including Data, Systems, Infrastructure, … Analysts). Please share your thoughts.” And here are some of the responses: “I  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:29:55.840Z"),
    "question" : "Which careers offers the best salary Business Analyst or QA analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 35 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603646e90c817f0398fa4a26"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Should-a-career-switch-be-made-from-a-business-analyst-to-a-software-developer?-",
    "answer" : "Now is the time you are building your career. If you feel and believe that a change will move you in the direction you want to pursue in your future, then I would do it now rather than waiting several more years. There is nothing wrong with either career. It comes down to where you will be the happiest and use the most and best of your skills in your work life. The general experience you have gained has helped you see what you do and don’t like about your job and I would use that to help me decide how to move forward. The one caution I would have is your comment about becoming self-reliant. No one can operate a business and be totally self-reliant. You will never know everything about everything it takes to operate your own firm. You will either hire independent contractors or staff to help  Continue Reading Now is the time you are building your career. If you feel and believe that a change will move you in the direction you want to pursue in your future, then I would do it now rather than waiting several more years. There is nothing wrong with either career. It comes down to where you will be the happiest and use the most and best of your skills in your work life. The general experience you have gained has helped you see what you do and don’t like about your job and I would use that to help me decide how to move forward. The one caution I would have is your comment about becoming self-reliant. No one can operate a business and be totally self-reliant. You will never know everything about everything it takes to operate your own firm. You will either hire independent contractors or staff to help  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:30:33.309Z"),
    "question" : "Should a career switch be made from a business analyst to a software developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 36 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603646f90c817f0398fa4a35"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-does-I-to-switch-career-from-QA-to-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Bobby Goodwin We BA's are occasionally asked, \"What do you do?\" I try to make a joke out of this innocent question by replying, \"Well, what would YOU do with English and writing degrees? I'm a Business Analyst of course.\" People don’t laugh. It's not because they don't want to make fun of an English major, it's because they don't have a clue what a Business Analyst does. You can't laugh at a joke if you don't get the punch line. It's true though, isn't it? Growing up to be a Business Analyst is not a dream that you've envisioned since childhood. However, since working with bright and talented computer folks for a decade or so, I've learned that it is a dream for many professionals to find their way into a career as a BA. My decision came when I spent several years working in software testing. That position Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:30:49.920Z"),
    "question" : "How does I to switch career from QA to business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 37 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036470c0c817f0398fa4a4a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-career-path-of-a-business-analyst-at-Google?-",
    "answer" : "Business analysts are responsible for identifying technology solutions to amorphous business problems. They can work in various industries like transportation, banking, telecommunications, healthcare, finance, etc. They analyze data to improve a company’s processes and products. The International Institute of Business Analysis describes a business analyst as one who identifies opportunities and executes them so that the business can capitalize on technology. Business analysts can specialize in different roles including functional, business systems, agile, or service requests depending on a person’s area of interest. For instance, a service request analyst is responsible for handling system enhancements along with inquiries from users while a functional analyst helps companies integrate their technology with other systems. Successful business analysts should be strong critical thinkers, problem solvers, and great communicators. He/she must be willing to take a holistic view of a challenge and work with different individuals to get the necessary information that drives technology changes. Mostly, those who do well as business analysts have previously worked as project managers or software developers. Job Responsibilities- Business Analyst Define business caseAnalyze what the business needsIdentify areas that need improvementResolving issues by working with various teamsRecommending suitable solutionsQuality testingProject developmentBusiness analysts can earn $78 500 per year.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:31:08.390Z"),
    "question" : "What is the career path of a business analyst at Google? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 38 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036471d0c817f0398fa4a98"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-best-domains-to-start-your-career-as-Business-Analyst-in-IT-industry?-",
    "answer" : "Well you do not always have a choice, but if you get one these are the best domains i believe according to job, growth and monetary prospects : Healthcare : Healthcare is an evergreen ever-growing domain. There are ample of opportunities and good money for Business Analysts having good experience and knowledge in this domain.Banking/Finance : Banking industry is famous for high paying jobs and growth opportunities, though this sector has seen some downfall in last few years, but still, it's one of the best domains to opt.Insurance : This is a niche sector which has seen good amount of growth in last couple of years.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:31:25.831Z"),
    "question" : "Which are the best domains to start your career as Business Analyst in IT industry? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 39 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603647440c817f0398fa4abe"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-should-I-build-my-career-as-a-freelance-Business-Analyst?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:32:04.185Z"),
    "question" : "How should I build my career as a freelance Business Analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 40 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603647560c817f0398fa4b0a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-a-business-analyst-and-data-science-career?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:32:22.635Z"),
    "question" : "What is a business analyst and data science career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 41 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036476a0c817f0398fa4b14"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Should-I-start-my-career-with-Business-Analyst-or-Software-development?-",
    "answer" : "Jeremy Aschenbrenner I think based on the more information you gave on the question, the Business Analyst route stands out.  The BA is responsible for doing exactly what you say, bridge the gap between the business and the technical/development team.  The wonderful thing about being a BA is you get to experience both the BA as well as dive into some of the technical details.   I think the BA route is also the best as it is the best platform to then transfer into software development (if you know languages) or as a QA tester.  There are companies that sometimes even have BAs do a little coding and testing.  So this is the best of all worlds. If you are interested in learning more about becoming a Business Analyst, my passion is to coach and mentor others so they can reach their dreams. There is no better feeling  Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:32:42.954Z"),
    "question" : "Should I start my career with Business Analyst or Software development? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 42 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036477b0c817f0398fa4b2a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-possible-to-start-a-career-as-a-business-analyst-after-engineering?-",
    "answer" : "Yes, it is easy if you get a campus placement. You would do well because of your analytical skills and mathematical bent of mind. But if you are out of college and searching for a job, then things would be very tough. Try to get anything at entry level where profile is good and relevant and be ready to slog + compromise on salary & other expectations. Otherwise do a MBA from a GRADE-1 college (only and only grade 1 with good placement record for Finance specialisation…tier 2 will be a disaster ).",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:32:59.348Z"),
    "question" : "Is it possible to start a career as a business analyst after engineering? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 43 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036478f0c817f0398fa4b74"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-change-career-to-business-analyst-from-banking-role?-",
    "answer" : "I will give you some ground realities of a banker trying to switch to business analysis. I can share this insight as a close acquaintance of mine is trying to move to a BA role and currently she is working in retail banking (India). Most of the BA job opportunities which come along are for experienced BA candidates. So as a banker, you may know about your domain but you do not have any prior BA knowledge hence you are not the best fit for experienced BA roles. You can do BA certified courses (Anisan, BCS etc) but again the bottom-line remains that you do not have actual BA experience. An organization can hire you as a BA but in that case your compensation may be at a fresher level only. To Sum it up, tough to move to a BA role if just have domain knowledge. Get BA certifications and then look Continue Reading I will give you some ground realities of a banker trying to switch to business analysis. I can share this insight as a close acquaintance of mine is trying to move to a BA role and currently she is working in retail banking (India). Most of the BA job opportunities which come along are for experienced BA candidates. So as a banker, you may know about your domain but you do not have any prior BA knowledge hence you are not the best fit for experienced BA roles. You can do BA certified courses (Anisan, BCS etc) but again the bottom-line remains that you do not have actual BA experience. An organization can hire you as a BA but in that case your compensation may be at a fresher level only. To Sum it up, tough to move to a BA role if just have domain knowledge. Get BA certifications and then look Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:33:19.135Z"),
    "question" : "How do I change career to business analyst from banking role? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 44 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603647a10c817f0398fa4b82"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-will-I-need-to-learn-in-order-to-start-a-career-as-a-data-analyst-or-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:33:37.414Z"),
    "question" : "What will I need to learn in order to start a career as a data analyst or business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 45 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603647b40c817f0398fa4b9a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Why-do-you-want-to-join-as-a-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Why do you want to be a business analyst?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:33:56.547Z"),
    "question" : "Why do you want to join as a business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 46 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603647c60c817f0398fa4bdc"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-get-a-job-in-data-analysis?-",
    "answer" : "That is a kind of a how do I hit the dartboard with a dart kind of question, in that it is really open ended with little details about you, your education, experience or interests. You don't have a lot on your profile but let me take a stab at this.Data Analysis jobs come in so many flavors and levels. First identify the 'vertical' or business category that you have functional knowledge over. For example, some functions like finance or HR can cross over verticals but business and technical analysis areas require topical context. So what do you know?How much do you know? What are your skills? Are you the king of Tableau, do you rock SAS or other analytics packages or are you a straight up SQL wunderkind? Pull these all together and start targeting the right level analyst roll using your Continue Reading That is a kind of a how do I hit the dartboard with a dart kind of question, in that it is really open ended with little details about you, your education, experience or interests. You don't have a lot on your profile but let me take a stab at this.Data Analysis jobs come in so many flavors and levels. First identify the 'vertical' or business category that you have functional knowledge over. For example, some functions like finance or HR can cross over verticals but business and technical analysis areas require topical context. So what do you know?How much do you know? What are your skills? Are you the king of Tableau, do you rock SAS or other analytics packages or are you a straight up SQL wunderkind? Pull these all together and start targeting the right level analyst roll using your Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:34:14.522Z"),
    "question" : "How do I get a job in data analysis? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 47 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603647d70c817f0398fa4bf0"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-way-to-change-my-career-from-being-a-Recruiter-to-a-Business-Analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Jeremy Aschenbrenner Always follow your passions!  Don't do a job just to pay the bills.  Find something you enjoy! I have been managing and hiring Business Analysts since 2012 and this is a very common question.  Breaking into the Business Analysis field is rather daunting when you don't know where to turn.  With your education and experience, you should have no issue landing your first job as a Business Analyst, as long as you have the foundational knowledge.  Here are the steps I would recommend: Identify your current skills that you can leverage as a Business Analyst.  Check out this YouTube video to understand the common Business Analyst Skills needed and based on being a Recruiter, skills you may already possess.Determine your best fitting Business Analyst roles.  There are at ton of roles. Some are techniContinue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:34:31.939Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best way to change my career from being a Recruiter to a Business Analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 48 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603647ec0c817f0398fa4c06"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-your-thoughts-on-a-career-as-a-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Bert Brijs Jamal, if your (internal) client appreciates your knowledge and skills as a business analyst, it is the best job in the world. Beware though of people who treat you as a waiter, taking orders instead of challenging requirements. In business analysis the adage “it is better to have a subject expert learning to program, than a programmer learning about the subject” is commonly accepted. But I have seen brilliant exceptions to that rule.For inspiration on the contents of the job, read about Volere requirements gathering from the Robertsons which is great stuff for application design and if you’re interested in Business Analysis for Business Intelligence –which people are slowly gathering as a separate, distinct discipline- I have to recommend my book with the exactly that title. Rinka Singh",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:34:52.829Z"),
    "question" : "What are your thoughts on a career as a business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 49 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603647fe0c817f0398fa4c16"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-does-a-Business-Analyst-launch-the-career?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How does a Business Analyst launch the career?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:35:10.345Z"),
    "question" : "How does a Business Analyst launch the career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 50 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603648260c817f0398fa4c74"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-does-a-Business-Analyst-career-progress?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How does a Business Analyst career progress?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:35:50.674Z"),
    "question" : "How does a Business Analyst career progress? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}
/* 1 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036484c0c817f0398fa4cce"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-being-a-business-analyst-a-good-start-for-my-career?-",
    "answer" : "Yes, and for several reasons. Business Analysts are in demand. This means that employment rates among BAs is very high and compensation is also above average.Career growth. Many BAs go on to fill senior management, project management or Consulting roles - or some combination of these.Stimulating work. Being a BA means you will be faced with interesting and challenging problems to solve for your clients. These will keep you busy and engaged, which is very important for leading a fulfilling career. Nikhil Tripathi",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:36:28.506Z"),
    "question" : "Is being a business analyst a good start for my career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036485e0c817f0398fa4cd8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-is-the-career-progression-as-a-Business-Analyst-in-banks-such-as-JP-Morgan-etc?-",
    "answer" : "Jamie Haberman From my experience across dozens of clients in banking (let's assume that the hierarchy is Managing Director>Director>Manager>Associate at the bottom):  Most common scenario (Associate & a few very experienced BAs may get the Manager just for salary purposes) - no career progression (ie stay as a BA); you get single digit percentages salary increases year-over-year; anecdotally, the majority of BAs that I've worked with were not interested in managing \"people\" or managing \"projects\" so they actually wanted to remain as BAsNext most common scenario (Manager) - generally the BA that's been around the longest tends to rise up to be the \"manager\" of the other BAs; you make a little more money, don't really get to make big decisions, have to do year-end performance reviews and are accountable foContinue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:36:46.310Z"),
    "question" : "How is the career progression as a Business Analyst in banks such as JP Morgan etc? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 3 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603648720c817f0398fa4cf0"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-is-a-CSM-certification-related-to-a-business-analyst-career?-",
    "answer" : "A CSM certificate is not necessarily tied to a business analysis career. You could be in any role and still be a Certified Scrum Master. A business analyst is the conduit of information between a client and the technical solution serving his requirements. Your role includes, but is not limited to, assessing client expectations, understanding business requirements and drafting algorithms that cater to your project. Now as a CSM, you add team and project management along with release planning. From a business analyst's perspective, this gives you a holistic view of the project you're working on, from initial requirements discussion to project planning and releasing. The one word of advice however I would have is, as a CSM, you're supposed to be a facilitator for the scrum team. You shouldn't l Continue Reading A CSM certificate is not necessarily tied to a business analysis career. You could be in any role and still be a Certified Scrum Master. A business analyst is the conduit of information between a client and the technical solution serving his requirements. Your role includes, but is not limited to, assessing client expectations, understanding business requirements and drafting algorithms that cater to your project. Now as a CSM, you add team and project management along with release planning. From a business analyst's perspective, this gives you a holistic view of the project you're working on, from initial requirements discussion to project planning and releasing. The one word of advice however I would have is, as a CSM, you're supposed to be a facilitator for the scrum team. You shouldn't l Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:37:06.614Z"),
    "question" : "How is a CSM certification related to a business analyst career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 4 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603648d00c817f0398fa4dae"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-start-working-as-a-data-analyst-or-a-business-analyst-with-a-different-career-background?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How can I start working as a data analyst or a business analyst with a different career background?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:38:40.196Z"),
    "question" : "How can I start working as a data analyst or a business analyst with a different career background? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 5 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603648f10c817f0398fa4e04"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-switch-my-career-to-a-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Yes, you can. The steps or the plan to switch will depend on your current profile and background. For example, if you are in Sales or you are a tester or a developer, your approach will differ. However the key steps should include the following: A) Understand the requirements and skills needed for becoming a BA B) Assess your current capabilities C) Plan to address the gap D) Get trained and certified E) Modify your resume F) Face interviews In any case, you should consider 8–12 weeks to complete all the above steps. You can visit our youtube channel for videos on these. For example, Moving from Sales to a BA role -",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:39:13.683Z"),
    "question" : "How do I switch my career to a business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 6 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603649070c817f0398fa4e18"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-way-to-create-business-analyst-career?-",
    "answer" : "A certificate helps but it is not the end-all and be-all.  Experience counts heavier imho.  Check what are the deliverables of a business analyst and apply it in your current job.  Treat them like projects and create a business analysis before embarking in them or if it has began or is over, create it to review if the project is on the right path.   Do not be harsh on the current or past project if you find that the path it has taken is illogical based on your analysis because the situation may have changed.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:39:35.215Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best way to create business analyst career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 7 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603649380c817f0398fa4e80"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-start-a-Business-Analyst-career-with-a-Banking-and-International-Business-background?-",
    "answer" : "As Lori Hamilton suggested, start with the IIBA, you will definitely want to read the BABOK. Then, try to find some Meetup groups related to IIBA, Business Analysts, and even Project Management. It's a wonderful experience to be able to converse with people who have this experience and a lot of the times, people attending are looking to poach, so you may end up with some opportunities. More importantly, take a look at your career, thus far. If needed, rewrite your resume to showcase your Business Analyst achievements. Try to show quantitive results in your projects. (i.e. time savings of 80% by transforming a manual process to a digital process, or automating process using specific tools, etc...) I believe you can perform business analysis in pretty much any role you are working. Always look Continue Reading As Lori Hamilton suggested, start with the IIBA, you will definitely want to read the BABOK. Then, try to find some Meetup groups related to IIBA, Business Analysts, and even Project Management. It's a wonderful experience to be able to converse with people who have this experience and a lot of the times, people attending are looking to poach, so you may end up with some opportunities. More importantly, take a look at your career, thus far. If needed, rewrite your resume to showcase your Business Analyst achievements. Try to show quantitive results in your projects. (i.e. time savings of 80% by transforming a manual process to a digital process, or automating process using specific tools, etc...) I believe you can perform business analysis in pretty much any role you are working. Always look Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:40:24.803Z"),
    "question" : "How do I start a Business Analyst career with a Banking and International Business background? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 8 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603649500c817f0398fa4e92"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-good-to-have-ECBA-certification-for-a-business-analysis-career?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:40:48.657Z"),
    "question" : "Is it good to have ECBA certification for a business analysis career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 9 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603649730c817f0398fa4ef2"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-career-growth-in-Wipro-Technologies-as-a-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Aditya Jadhav",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:41:23.929Z"),
    "question" : "What is the career growth in Wipro Technologies as a business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 10 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603649960c817f0398fa4f0e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-career-path-for-a-business-analyst-at-Amazon?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:41:58.299Z"),
    "question" : "What is the career path for a business analyst at Amazon? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 11 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603649a80c817f0398fa4f52"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-career-is-good-business-analyst-or-Hr?-",
    "answer" : "The below points will make you understand whether to start career as Business Analyst or HR. Please choose your career carefully: Is money your priority?: If yes then HR would not be a good option as HR team will not be a Revenue centre in any company. Business analyst would be a better option.Quality of work: HR would be involved in recruiting or employee engagement activities at the other end Business analyst will be involved in many activities from requirement gathering to testing to handeling clients etc (depending on your capabilities).Job opportunities: Business analyst will have more job opportunities than HR employees. Because small to mid sized companies hire only small no of HRs (2–3). But you will find more no of BAs in market. So job opportunities are more for BAs.Competition: LContinue Reading The below points will make you understand whether to start career as Business Analyst or HR. Please choose your career carefully: Is money your priority?: If yes then HR would not be a good option as HR team will not be a Revenue centre in any company. Business analyst would be a better option.Quality of work: HR would be involved in recruiting or employee engagement activities at the other end Business analyst will be involved in many activities from requirement gathering to testing to handeling clients etc (depending on your capabilities).Job opportunities: Business analyst will have more job opportunities than HR employees. Because small to mid sized companies hire only small no of HRs (2–3). But you will find more no of BAs in market. So job opportunities are more for BAs.Competition: LContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:42:16.588Z"),
    "question" : "Which career is good business analyst or Hr? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 12 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603649cd0c817f0398fa4f7c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-a-software-developer-switch-his-career-to-become-a-business-analyst-in-IT?-",
    "answer" : "Certifications are always a good way to learn and probably a good way to obtain a jr. position if you are making a career transition. I would also consider looking at one of the large consulting firms (Accenture, E&Y, etc.) that would probably be happy to bring in someone with both an interest in development and BA. I was with Accenture for 9.5 years as a developer/tech lead but I gained enough exposure to the BA role that I could easily perform it myself.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:42:53.352Z"),
    "question" : "How can a software developer switch his career to become a business analyst in IT? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603649dd0c817f0398fa4f87"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-becoming-a-Salesforce-Admin-a-good-choice-for-a-Business-Analyst-career-growth?-",
    "answer" : "Probably not.  A Sysadmin job is highly technical and one of those jobs that doesn't have exposure to the business and if you want to be a Business Analyst you must have some exposure to the business. If you are still going after a technical job with the hopes of moving to the BA role you're better off becoming a developer or even tech support because those roles at least give you exposure to the functional requirements of the application. This puts you in a better spot because you'll learn about the product and be able to relate to the client more naturally. Drew Weaver",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:43:09.552Z"),
    "question" : "Is becoming a Salesforce Admin a good choice for a Business Analyst career growth? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 14 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364a130c817f0398fa4fee"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-career-opportunities-for-the-roles-of-an-ERP-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Sandhya Jane ERP offers plenty of options as it is used in most companies, small or large all need ERP in different ways. Some companies prefer to use their in-house ERP, some use off-the-shelf products, and some use customised off-the-shelf products. Business Analyst plays crucial role in defining requirements/features, customisation, user experience and so more…These implementations are critical to company’s operations that can make or break a company. (for example, “The company noted that it subsequently discovered that the new system \"did not yet provide accurate inventory count numbers,\" causing Shane to become \"substantially overstocked with inventory, and with the wrong mix of inventory.\" That added to Shane's capital costs and affected sales for the rest of 2007 and the first nine months of 2008 Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:44:03.810Z"),
    "question" : "What are the career opportunities for the roles of an ERP business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 15 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364a270c817f0398fa503a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-a-commerce-graduate-become-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Can a commerce graduate become business analyst?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:44:23.010Z"),
    "question" : "Can a commerce graduate become business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 16 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364a900c817f0398fa50cc"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-a-business-analyst-add-value-to-his-career?-",
    "answer" : "Beyond formal job descriptions, day-to-day responsibilities, acting as an intermediary between different stakeholders, the ultimate job of a BA is to create value for your project/company. And this naturally leads to adding value to the BA’s own career. The key is to play to your strengths as a generalist (breadth), ANDdevelop specialties in one or two areas (depth)This is often referred to as the T-type professional: combining breadth and depth.  Breadth is what you’re already good at — such as working across the organization with a variety of stakeholders, understanding the different technologies used in projects, mastering the client’s business in each project, etc. Depth is one or two areas that you should specialize in — such as enterprise architecting, domain subject matter expertise (e.g. insurance), process expertise (e.g. Kanban), etc.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:46:08.594Z"),
    "question" : "How can a business analyst add value to his career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 17 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364ace0c817f0398fa513b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-certification-offers-the-best-career-leverage-for-individuals-in-business-analyst-roles?-",
    "answer" : "It's very hard to say.  Being a business analyst means u need a lot of differnt skills and the least could be IT.  U could be perfect at all things computer science. But bad at communications. And the people's are engineering requirements from will never get what they want.  U could be awesome at communications and ur manager would never know ur crap but the programmers in IT would....but does that make u bad? The guy signing ur paycheck doesn't think ur bad.  I know a business analyst who was perfect at creating designs engineered from use cases, it was very easy to read the design and to maintain and build on top of.  But he was bad at explaining to the business why they couldn't get a cheaper solution because to them cheaper was better, always. But theirs was only the cheapest if u didn't c Continue Reading It's very hard to say.  Being a business analyst means u need a lot of differnt skills and the least could be IT.  U could be perfect at all things computer science. But bad at communications. And the people's are engineering requirements from will never get what they want.  U could be awesome at communications and ur manager would never know ur crap but the programmers in IT would....but does that make u bad? The guy signing ur paycheck doesn't think ur bad.  I know a business analyst who was perfect at creating designs engineered from use cases, it was very easy to read the design and to maintain and build on top of.  But he was bad at explaining to the business why they couldn't get a cheaper solution because to them cheaper was better, always. But theirs was only the cheapest if u didn't c Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:47:10.193Z"),
    "question" : "What certification offers the best career leverage for individuals in business analyst roles? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 18 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364ae10c817f0398fa5184"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-career-path-for-a-business-analyst?-Is-business-analyst-a-good-career?-",
    "answer" : "Business Analyst Career Progression We will first explore the foundational knowledge and skills needed in the early part of a business analysts' career and then what is required to progress. Entry-level Business Analyst From a foundational knowledge perspective, the first thing a BA must possess is some technical aptitude. This does not mean a BA has to have a degree in Management Information Systems, or Software Engineering but they do have to understand what a software application is and how it works i.e. processes translate to logic, data is information the business cares about, business rules govern the way a business operates. The reason this knowledge is important is because most BA's will start their careers at the project level working on software enhancements and implementations. In  Continue Reading Business Analyst Career Progression We will first explore the foundational knowledge and skills needed in the early part of a business analysts' career and then what is required to progress. Entry-level Business Analyst From a foundational knowledge perspective, the first thing a BA must possess is some technical aptitude. This does not mean a BA has to have a degree in Management Information Systems, or Software Engineering but they do have to understand what a software application is and how it works i.e. processes translate to logic, data is information the business cares about, business rules govern the way a business operates. The reason this knowledge is important is because most BA's will start their careers at the project level working on software enhancements and implementations. In  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:47:29.441Z"),
    "question" : "What is the career path for a Business Analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 19 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364b050c817f0398fa51a4"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-make-a-good-career-in-the-data-analytics-industry?-What-are-the-skills-I-need-to-develop-if-I-have-to-start-from-scratch?-",
    "answer" : "Data analytics has gained humongous popularity over the past few years and has become a hot topic in the market since data is at the core of the technology. Demand for data analysts with the right skill set and knowledge will keep increasing with billions of data getting generated every day. There is an umpteenth number of opportunities that span across multiple industries for you to explore since making a career in analytics is promising for people of all backgrounds. Let's find out why one should pursue a Career in Data Analytics? High salary at entry-level and excellent perks - Data analysts are paid very well in the industry even at entry-level since there are limited data analysts in the market. Data analysis is one of the most sought after jobs in the market and there is no denying tha Continue Reading Data analytics has gained humongous popularity over the past few years and has become a hot topic in the market since data is at the core of the technology. Demand for data analysts with the right skill set and knowledge will keep increasing with billions of data getting generated every day. There is an umpteenth number of opportunities that span across multiple industries for you to explore since making a career in analytics is promising for people of all backgrounds. Let's find out why one should pursue a Career in Data Analytics? High salary at entry-level and excellent perks - Data analysts are paid very well in the industry even at entry-level since there are limited data analysts in the market. Data analysis is one of the most sought after jobs in the market and there is no denying tha Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:48:05.812Z"),
    "question" : "How can I make a good career in the data analytics industry? What are the skills I need to develop if I have to start from scratch? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 20 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364b180c817f0398fa51f0"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-certification-for-a-fresher-to-start-a-career-as-a-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the best certification for a fresher to start a career as a business analyst?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:48:24.304Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best certification for a fresher to start a career as a business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 21 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364b290c817f0398fa51fa"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-possible-to-switch-your-career-from-Marketing-or-sales-to-Business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Is it possible to switch your career from Marketing or sales to Business analyst?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:48:41.726Z"),
    "question" : "Is it possible to switch your career from Marketing or sales to Business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 22 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364b3a0c817f0398fa520f"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-career-option-for-business-analyst-freelancing?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:48:58.368Z"),
    "question" : "What is the career option for business analyst freelancing? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 23 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364b4c0c817f0398fa5252"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-of-the-best-business-analytics-certification-courses-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Hi All, I have recently completed Business Analytics course on UpGrad and believe me I never thought it would be such an ease to complete this 3 months certification without skipping my work. During this pandemic as everyone started working from home I was really looking for a job change and upskill myself. It’s then and a friend of mine told me about UpGrad BA certification. The reason being I wanted to switch to BA role or into similar functional role. UpGrad is a very neatly designed learning platform. Right from the application to the enrolment, beginning till the course ends it provides you with proper guidance. Below are some highlights: They have a student mentor for every course and every student who ensures that your queries are answered.They have live sessions which will be hosted oContinue Reading Hi All, I have recently completed Business Analytics course on UpGrad and believe me I never thought it would be such an ease to complete this 3 months certification without skipping my work. During this pandemic as everyone started working from home I was really looking for a job change and upskill myself. It’s then and a friend of mine told me about UpGrad BA certification. The reason being I wanted to switch to BA role or into similar functional role. UpGrad is a very neatly designed learning platform. Right from the application to the enrolment, beginning till the course ends it provides you with proper guidance. Below are some highlights: They have a student mentor for every course and every student who ensures that your queries are answered.They have live sessions which will be hosted oContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:49:16.230Z"),
    "question" : "What are some of the best business analytics certification courses in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 24 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364b830c817f0398fa52bc"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-switch-my-career-to-a-business-analyst-from-a-test-engineer?-",
    "answer" : "Thank you for the A2A! I would suggest speaking to your manager about a role change. The chances of becoming a BA by role change in your current company are far more than actually looking for a job switch that gives you the role of BA without any experience. But your company should be willing to trust you to do the role efficiently. Since you are a de facto BA in your current organisation, it should be easier for you. If your organisation is sceptical then you could start by shadowing a designated BA to learn the ropes. Getting a certification especially by the likes of IIBA might also help. The ECBA certificate is targeted at: Individuals entering the BA profession:Students enrolled in BA academic programsNew graduatesProfessionals transitioning careersFunctional managers who are not BAs but maContinue Reading Thank you for the A2A! I would suggest speaking to your manager about a role change. The chances of becoming a BA by role change in your current company are far more than actually looking for a job switch that gives you the role of BA without any experience. But your company should be willing to trust you to do the role efficiently. Since you are a de facto BA in your current organisation, it should be easier for you. If your organisation is sceptical then you could start by shadowing a designated BA to learn the ropes. Getting a certification especially by the likes of IIBA might also help. The ECBA certificate is targeted at: Individuals entering the BA profession:Students enrolled in BA academic programsNew graduatesProfessionals transitioning careersFunctional managers who are not BAs but maContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:50:11.955Z"),
    "question" : "How can I switch my career to a business analyst from a test engineer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 25 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364ba40c817f0398fa52dc"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-change-my-career-from-IT-Business-Analyst-to-Financial-Analyst?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:50:44.389Z"),
    "question" : "How can I change my career from IT Business Analyst to Financial Analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 26 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364bcc0c817f0398fa533e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-business-analyst-a-good-career-to-choose-for-2020-and-beyond?-",
    "answer" : "Business analysis is a profession which enables the changes within an enterprise by clarifying the requirements and providing the solutions for the business stakeholders. A business analyst is a role where one can contribute to an organization’s strategy, its offerings, its revenue, and its margin. Business analysts work as a bridge between business stakeholders and technology architects. Business analysts enable an enterprise to articulate its needs and the rationale for change and to design and describe solutions that deliver value. Business analysts, understand the problems and goals of an enterprise, analyze needs and solutions, devise change strategies, drive change, collaborate with stakeholders and also advise organizations on improving efficiency, finances, and various other aspects  Continue Reading Business analysis is a profession which enables the changes within an enterprise by clarifying the requirements and providing the solutions for the business stakeholders. A business analyst is a role where one can contribute to an organization’s strategy, its offerings, its revenue, and its margin. Business analysts work as a bridge between business stakeholders and technology architects. Business analysts enable an enterprise to articulate its needs and the rationale for change and to design and describe solutions that deliver value. Business analysts, understand the problems and goals of an enterprise, analyze needs and solutions, devise change strategies, drive change, collaborate with stakeholders and also advise organizations on improving efficiency, finances, and various other aspects  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:51:24.085Z"),
    "question" : "Is business analyst a good career to choose for 2020 and beyond? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 27 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364bf00c817f0398fa535b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-change-my-career-from-business-analyst-in-consulting-to-business-analyst-in-IT?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Drew Weaver 1",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:52:00.184Z"),
    "question" : "How can I change my career from business analyst in consulting to business analyst in IT? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 28 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364c380c817f0398fa5405"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-would-be-the-roles-and-career-paths-of-a-business-consultant-and-a-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "To my understanding an analyst is a junior and a consultant is a senior. Basically analyst/associate are the entry level designations in any organisation and consultant/developer are immediate senior level designation. While an analyst you rely on mentoring and seniors for daily jobs while after becoming a senior like consultant you will be accountable and expected to work on your own and take decisions.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:53:12.368Z"),
    "question" : "What would be the roles and career paths of a business consultant and a business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 29 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364c490c817f0398fa5419"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-change-my-career-to-Business-Analyst-role?-",
    "answer" : "I don’t know whether I am right person as you are more experienced then me but surely I can share my experience with you. I am working as a BA in Accenture for last 2 years. I am not MBA I have done engineering in CS but fortunately I was trained as BA and got project for same. You are already MBA you know better than me but for BA you have to be skilled in few areas like requirement gathering, building usecases, workflows, how to facilitate brainstorming/focus group sessions etc etc. What you can do Start preparing for IIBA certification CCBA or CBAP, get certified then try to make a switch you will get many opportunities. If you need learning material I can help you with that. If you want to be BA also be ready to to testing lots of testing. Being developer you might have received recognition Continue Reading I don’t know whether I am right person as you are more experienced then me but surely I can share my experience with you. I am working as a BA in Accenture for last 2 years. I am not MBA I have done engineering in CS but fortunately I was trained as BA and got project for same. You are already MBA you know better than me but for BA you have to be skilled in few areas like requirement gathering, building usecases, workflows, how to facilitate brainstorming/focus group sessions etc etc. What you can do Start preparing for IIBA certification CCBA or CBAP, get certified then try to make a switch you will get many opportunities. If you need learning material I can help you with that. If you want to be BA also be ready to to testing lots of testing. Being developer you might have received recognition Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:53:29.912Z"),
    "question" : "How can I change my career to Business Analyst role? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 30 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364c5f0c817f0398fa542c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-promising-is-a-career-as-business-analyst-for-healthcare-IT?-",
    "answer" : "While health care is transforming itself at a quick pace from the traditional systems to now automated processes, it becomes vital for managing this transformation in a most efficient and productive manner. Most of the current systems in health care are either underused or fail after few days of implementations. One of the main reason is the lack of proper understanding of end users. In health care, end user’s requirements are more personalized as each user has his/her style of practice. The role of a business analyst is vital when it comes to the development and implantation of any IT systems in a health care setting. The main purpose within health care would be to extract user requirements (as they play a key role in the success of any systems) and present them in a most understandable ma Continue Reading While health care is transforming itself at a quick pace from the traditional systems to now automated processes, it becomes vital for managing this transformation in a most efficient and productive manner. Most of the current systems in health care are either underused or fail after few days of implementations. One of the main reason is the lack of proper understanding of end users. In health care, end user’s requirements are more personalized as each user has his/her style of practice. The role of a business analyst is vital when it comes to the development and implantation of any IT systems in a health care setting. The main purpose within health care would be to extract user requirements (as they play a key role in the success of any systems) and present them in a most understandable ma Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:53:51.060Z"),
    "question" : "How promising is a career as business analyst for healthcare IT? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 31 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364c840c817f0398fa5486"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-career-path-should-I-choose-from-sales-to-a-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Thanks for the A2A. Firstly , As a person who has moved from Sales to Business Analysis, let me tell you it is not a easy task. I was successful because i had the skills for a Business Analyst from a prior job. Personal view is this. Identify the skills that you would need to succeed in a BA role. Such as, Ability to understand a client and matching those requirements to what can be developed. Ability to document requirements. Analysis and breaking complex problems into blocks Solution design Tracking and closure Client and stakeholder management etc.. As a sales person, if you are managing a team and report to a boss or a client you do many of these things on a regular basis but they are not structured. You do not document each interaction. This is because the focus in Sales is to get the task done  Continue Reading Thanks for the A2A. Firstly , As a person who has moved from Sales to Business Analysis, let me tell you it is not a easy task. I was successful because i had the skills for a Business Analyst from a prior job. Personal view is this. Identify the skills that you would need to succeed in a BA role. Such as, Ability to understand a client and matching those requirements to what can be developed. Ability to document requirements. Analysis and breaking complex problems into blocks Solution design Tracking and closure Client and stakeholder management etc.. As a sales person, if you are managing a team and report to a boss or a client you do many of these things on a regular basis but they are not structured. You do not document each interaction. This is because the focus in Sales is to get the task done  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:54:28.751Z"),
    "question" : "What career path should I choose from sales to a business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 32 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364c950c817f0398fa5492"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-a-good-idea-to-change-my-career-as-a-web-developer-to-a-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Both careers are in high demand, and closely aligned. Moving from web developer to business analyst is a path that many people choose. It depends on what you love to do. As a business analyst, especially if you are working in a company that delivers bespoke (customised) software to enterprise clients, your background in web development will make it easy for you to quickly identify issues and communicate them to developers efficiently (or, in a crisis, possibly fix them yourself). As a BA, you’ll probably spend far more time dealing with new people though so you should consider if that is something that you would enjoy.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:54:45.412Z"),
    "question" : "Is it a good idea to change my career as a web developer to a business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 33 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364cba0c817f0398fa54f2"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-switch-my-career-domain-from-Digital-marketing-to-Business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Sumanth Cheedella Shiv Bhaker Sam Reader",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:55:22.199Z"),
    "question" : "How do I switch my career domain from Digital marketing to Business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 34 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364ccb0c817f0398fa54ff"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-career-opportunities-for-the-role-of-technical-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "The role of a Business Analyst is a messy one and rarely clearly defined in any organization. Some will want technical skills, sometimes to extreme - what they really want is a developer who has analytical skills (a rarity), or you will see many job postings that include a lot of requirements that fit in to the role of a Quality Assurance person. The BA role has always been a confusing and poorly defined space. If you are technical and you enjoy doing analyst work (which is exactly how I roll), then I suggest actually  searching for positions that are titled \"Technical Business Analyst\" or \"Business Systems Analyst\" as these are types of roles are usually going to allow you to utilize your analysis and technical skills.   If you aren't technical, then quickly scan those postings and move on. Do not take jobs that require skills you don't enjoy using. Which is not the same as saying don't take a job where you don't have the required skills. Job postings are \"wish lists\" and are almost always flexible. The same goes for so-called education requirements. I have no degree, but I do have 140+ hours of college credit - I don't have a degree but I do have an extensive education.  The only time I skip over a position with a degree requirement is when they are looking for someone with a Masters or higher, because clearly they want a degree higher than my level of education and putting a Masters+ as a requirement also usually means that they aren't going to negotiate the education level. One more thing to consider is the difference between having a Technical Skill (I can write SQL queries, complex SQL queries, build databases) versus having an understanding of a technical skill (I can read SQL queries, work with result sets to create reports, analyze the data that comes from the database). Many job postings will ask for a Technical BA, and what they really want is someone who has a deep understanding of technology, not necessarily being able to perform the work of a technologist. So be sure and read specific requirements carefully to determine which they really want: Prior experience working in a SQL environment and creating reports from data sets using a variety of tools.Prior experience writing creating SQL queries, extracting data, using Tableau to create reports and design dashboards.The first wants understanding and some skill and using the data results to analyze and create reports. The second is asking for a hard technical skill, you will be writing queries, extracting data, etc...  In my case, for example, I can write SQL and complex SQL, but I can only read code, I used to write code a long time ago, but I have no practical skill today that allows me to create actual code.  So back to the question - what are career opportunities for a tech BA - here are some common  job titles you might see: Technical Business AnalystSenior Technical Business AnalystBusiness Systems AnalystSenior Business Systems AnalystBusiness Process Analyst for Technology TeamBusiness Process Analyst for IT DepartmentThose are just a  few of the potential job titles you will find. Here are a couple of great websites that you can explore for more information on the role of a Business Analyst.  The Professional Association dedicated to promoting the business analysis profession worldwide - IIBA  Bridging the Gap  Business Analyst Certification | PBA   Good luck!",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:55:39.818Z"),
    "question" : "What are career opportunities for the role of technical business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 35 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364d010c817f0398fa5568"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-will-be-the-career-growth-for-business-technology-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:56:33.974Z"),
    "question" : "What will be the career growth for business technology analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 36 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364d220c817f0398fa5588"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-a-better-career-opportunity-systems-analyst-or-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "In general, these two terms are used for the similar profiles. These are used to refer to the professionals who work with the stakeholders for gathering requirements, analysing and modelling the requirements and creating SRS/FRD/FSD documents. In Agile environment, the documentation may be limited but the activities remain the same. However, it is also important to note that in some organisations, a Systems Analyst may be used to refer to a Business analyst who also has knowledge on systems, technology and tech platforms.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:57:06.229Z"),
    "question" : "Which is a better career opportunity systems analyst or business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 37 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364d5a0c817f0398fa55f2"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-switch-careers-to-a-business-analyst-from-QA?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Ani Oko 2",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:58:02.874Z"),
    "question" : "How do I switch careers to a business analyst from QA? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 38 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364d9d0c817f0398fa5662"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-career-advice-would-you-give-to-someone-who-wants-to-become-a-Business-Systems-Analysts?-",
    "answer" : "It’s one of the toughest job but looks like the easiest one. You need to have a good understanding of both development and test life cycle. You also need to have a sound understanding of the business knowledge of the industry. Go for some standard market recognized certifications. Another thing I would suggest is some analytics based certification will be an good advantage. Understanding the business is the Key here.(This doesnot mean that you must know everything or you must know how to write each code).Understanding Business will facilitate your growth.You must know Challenges at ground level.You must be qualified and possess good writing and verbal communication skills. Technical knowledge and Understanding of business processes will be the key differentiator.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:59:09.336Z"),
    "question" : "What career advice would you give to someone who wants to become a Business Systems Analysts? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 39 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364db60c817f0398fa56ae"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-start-a-career-as-a-business-consultant-or-analyst-at-an-MNC?-",
    "answer" : "Business consultants bring years of experience to bear on solving business problems. No one hires beginning business consultants. These are more end of career positions than start of career. On the other hand there are junior level business analysis openings at most MNCs. They will probably require a couple of years of experience but if you are going to succeed as a business analyst you should be able to analyze your own experience and explain how that fills the needs of the position that you are applying for. 1",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T12:59:34.359Z"),
    "question" : "How can I start a career as a business consultant or analyst at an MNC? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 40 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364dfc0c817f0398fa5724"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-switch-to-a-business-analyst-from-an-IT-career?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How can I switch my career to investment banking from an IT Business analyst?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:00:44.728Z"),
    "question" : "How can I switch to a business analyst from an IT career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 41 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364e230c817f0398fa5786"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-start-a-business-analyst-career-with-political-studies-background?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Donna Shelby",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:01:23.863Z"),
    "question" : "How do I start a business analyst career with political studies background? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 42 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364e470c817f0398fa57a2"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-switch-to-business-analyst-from-business-objects-career?-",
    "answer" : "I would love to answer this. Note:- BA is a very vast profile and has no single definition, I will keep my answer relative to your question. I started my career as a Business Objects Consultant and gradually evolved as a Business Analyst. Suggestions: Need - Understand the business need of the reports & dashboards. What do they do of these reports ?What are the KPIs getting calculated in the report ?What is this chart ?Ask these questions, this will gradually help in building the business knowledge. Dig into Data - Get behind the reports, understand the universe, data model and business rules. Interact More - Any report developer works closely with the customer, interactions gives you confidence and in no time you are ready for a client facing role. Documentation - Get familiar with documentation, Continue Reading I would love to answer this. Note:- BA is a very vast profile and has no single definition, I will keep my answer relative to your question. I started my career as a Business Objects Consultant and gradually evolved as a Business Analyst. Suggestions: Need - Understand the business need of the reports & dashboards. What do they do of these reports ?What are the KPIs getting calculated in the report ?What is this chart ?Ask these questions, this will gradually help in building the business knowledge. Dig into Data - Get behind the reports, understand the universe, data model and business rules. Interact More - Any report developer works closely with the customer, interactions gives you confidence and in no time you are ready for a client facing role. Documentation - Get familiar with documentation, Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:01:59.568Z"),
    "question" : "How can I switch to business analyst from business objects career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 43 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364e5b0c817f0398fa57ea"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-some-career-advice-for-a-business-analyst-with-development-experience?-",
    "answer" : "Vijay S Shukla, Principal Consultant and Trainer at QBI Institute (2010-present)Answered 3 years agoWhat is some career advice for a business analyst with development experience? Vijay S Shukla Dear Fellow Professional First of all I must congratulate you that you have an excellent background to start off your Business analyst career. A business analyst requires three set of skillsTechnical Skills : Requirements Elicitation, Analysis, Documentation, Validation, Modelling etc. SQL and RDBMS skills, Systems thinking, Methodologies : Agile, RUP. Technologies and standard important to your domain etcBusiness Skills : Domain Vocabulary, Domain Rules, Process knowledge, Business drivers, Industry trends etcCommunication, Project and Leadership skillsThough you can continue to hone each three areas you can work more on part b. Go through news paper articles, speacialist magazines and research papers for the business domain you are working in, on a daily basis. You have to dig deep and beContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:02:19.037Z"),
    "question" : "What is some career advice for a business analyst with development experience? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 44 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364e7d0c817f0398fa5810"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-initial-course-to-start-a-career-as-a-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Hello Savi, The most recognized entry level BA certification is ECBA from IIBA. You can learn more about the same at AdaptiveUS.com/ECBA. Regards LN",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:02:53.186Z"),
    "question" : "What is the initial course to start a career as a business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 45 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364ec90c817f0398fa5882"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-a-graduate-of-chemical-engineering-make-a-career-in-business-analysis?-",
    "answer" : "If you want to be directly related, then you become an analyst in a field directly related to chemical engineering. Preferably, since you are a chemical engineer, you would have worked in that field before becoming an analyst. Fields include chemicals, o&g, pharma/biopharma, materials, renewables, etc. Obviously there is more to business analysis than what you would learn in chemical engineering, but having the in field experience would be a strong asset to an analyst firm William Gorman",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:04:09.012Z"),
    "question" : "How can a graduate of chemical engineering make a career in business analysis? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 46 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364edd0c817f0398fa58ce"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-should-a-business-analyst-plan-his-career?-",
    "answer" : "Great question; as one plans anything worth doing. Start with what you need in terms of skills and begin a plan to acquire them. Know as a skills assessment this will help you plan out the next 5–10 years of your professional life. Step one: visit the IIBAs website and take the skills test Step two: get a copy of V3 of the BABOK and take a look at the knowledge areas and the tasks within. You are looking for things you've already done so you can frame your resume it the right way. Since PM and BA work is more or less the same, from project to project it's best that you structure your resume in a project by project fashion. Highlight things like objectives, deliverables, budget, solution proposed and solution delivered. Also any major risk and issues encountered. That should get you stated. Touch base with us once you have completed a skills assessment and you resume is in order. We can discuss training and getting the first job.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:04:29.193Z"),
    "question" : "How should a business analyst plan his career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 47 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364f030c817f0398fa58f0"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-high-paying-career-business-analyst-or-investment-banker?-",
    "answer" : "If you are into front-end role in an investment bank, then that will definitely fetch you a heftier package than a business analyst. Areas like consulting and Investment banking rely heavily on bonuses. If you are a good performer and market is in a good shape, then your bonus may exceed your base pay package increasing your overall salary. However, in business analyst role you will be working internally for a company (in most of the situations), so your bonus component will be the usual one, same as other employees in the organization. You might have a higher base package than an investment banker but your overall yearly salary may be less than an investment banker. 10",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:05:07.085Z"),
    "question" : "What is high paying career business analyst or investment banker? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 48 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364f140c817f0398fa593c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-is-the-career-of-a-business-analyst-in-an-IT-company-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Business Analyst as a profession in the IT sector has always been lucrative. This is because the Business Analyst (BA) would be the single-point-of-contact between the Customer and the Delivery team. As the IT industry matured, today, the role of a Business Analyst has also matured bringing in the good practices. After the e-Commerce and the Cloud boom, the jargons and lingos have been rephrased for the marketing purpose. Today, everything you see is all about experience - User Experience, Customer Experience, Student Experience, Employee Experience, etc. Today, the Business Analyst is very much interested to be known as Customer Experience Analyst. This aligns better than business analyst. Being a Customer Experience Analyst (CXA), you end-up preparing a customer-journey mapping to arrive at Continue Reading Business Analyst as a profession in the IT sector has always been lucrative. This is because the Business Analyst (BA) would be the single-point-of-contact between the Customer and the Delivery team. As the IT industry matured, today, the role of a Business Analyst has also matured bringing in the good practices. After the e-Commerce and the Cloud boom, the jargons and lingos have been rephrased for the marketing purpose. Today, everything you see is all about experience - User Experience, Customer Experience, Student Experience, Employee Experience, etc. Today, the Business Analyst is very much interested to be known as Customer Experience Analyst. This aligns better than business analyst. Being a Customer Experience Analyst (CXA), you end-up preparing a customer-journey mapping to arrive at Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:05:24.636Z"),
    "question" : "How is the career of a business analyst in an IT company in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 49 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364f3c0c817f0398fa5962"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Will-an-MS-in-Business-Analytics-be-a-great-way-into-a-career-as-an-Operations-Research-Analyst?-",
    "answer" : "Sivabala Munees Simple answer No. Here is why it is a no, Operation research analyst is heavier in understanding the operations, supply chain , inventory and logistics management. The data component is only about these areas and then there is the larger  optimization component to it where you will be required to develop mathematical models. Some of the applications may be like a transportation path optimization(Network), location determination model(Distrubution centre/Warhouse location), inventory optimization models. If you see all of these you need minimal data skills but a very good understanding of Operations Research methods. As an analyst you may often not built models from ground up alone, but if you really want to progress in the Operations path then you certainly be very good in the basic mathema Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:06:04.544Z"),
    "question" : "Will an MS in Business Analytics be a great way into a career as an Operations Research Analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 50 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364f620c817f0398fa59b4"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-a-market-research-analyst-switch-his-career-to-a-business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:06:42.628Z"),
    "question" : "Can a market research analyst switch his career to a business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}
/* 1 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364f770c817f0398fa59ce"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-becoming-a-business-analyst-a-career-still-considered-relevant-today?-",
    "answer" : "Yes, it is still relevant. I think the big potential threat to the profession may be in tools to automate insights as business analysts often are more experts in creating powerpoints, and focusing on analytical work for improving the business function. It is possible in the longer term that improved tools will make members of the profession more capable of working quickly, and maybe push for splits within the business analyst profession. (as in maybe instead of a unified profession, you’ll see even more exaggerated splits between “analytics product owners”, “business data analysts” and “powerpoint experts/product analysts”) However, if you manage your career well, you should be able to survive. No matter what, ML algorithms need human judgment to interpret, and there need to be people with e Continue Reading Yes, it is still relevant. I think the big potential threat to the profession may be in tools to automate insights as business analysts often are more experts in creating powerpoints, and focusing on analytical work for improving the business function. It is possible in the longer term that improved tools will make members of the profession more capable of working quickly, and maybe push for splits within the business analyst profession. (as in maybe instead of a unified profession, you’ll see even more exaggerated splits between “analytics product owners”, “business data analysts” and “powerpoint experts/product analysts”) However, if you manage your career well, you should be able to survive. No matter what, ML algorithms need human judgment to interpret, and there need to be people with e Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:07:03.902Z"),
    "question" : "Is becoming a business analyst a career still considered relevant today? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364f870c817f0398fa5a17"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-start-a-business-analyst-career-with-HR-recruiter-background?-",
    "answer" : "Shantanu Dhankar Your best bet would be look for a functional HRMS consultant opportunity. ERP systems like peoplesoft (now oracle) have got such modules,  since you have an HR background and I assume you must be well aware of the HR processes, you can get your foot in the door as a functional consultant. Once you have made to this point then it is up to you to pick up other aspects/ other modules and expand on your skills. There are many training institutes which provide BA training , you may join them to gain knowledge but not sure if they come with a placement gaurantee. CCBA/CBAP is an industry recognized BA certification but it needs prior experience as a BA to appear for these exams. Sushant Binakar",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:07:19.772Z"),
    "question" : "How do I start a business analyst career with HR recruiter background? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 3 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364fad0c817f0398fa5a38"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-IT-courses-and-certifications-do-you-need-to-start-a-fresh-career-in-Business-Analyst?-",
    "answer" : "A business anlayst shpould have both technical and domain skills. So a buisness anlayst in the finance domain should have in depth knowledge of both IT and finance . Also a business analyst should have the ability to create use cases, business process models ,workflow models and prototypes. There are many BA courses and certifications available online .The International Institute Of Business Analysis is a premier institute is a premier institute that offers various certifications. They have courses in four levels. Level1-ECBA Level2-CCBA Level3-CBAP Level4-CBATL They also have several training sessions and webinars and also provide course materials. You can check their website for more information. Also I would suggest doing some certifications in the domain you are interested in. Also get well versed in UML and Microsoft Visio. It will help you tremendously in understanding and creating use cases and flow diagrams. It also helps if the BA has a bit of a testing background. Almost all good BA’s have some testing background.Therefore they understand their the application from the end user’s point of view .So ISTQB certification in software testing can help tremendously.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:07:57.407Z"),
    "question" : "What IT courses and certifications do you need to start a fresh career in Business Analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 4 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364fe40c817f0398fa5aa0"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-scope-of-a-chartered-accountant-in-the-business-analyst-career-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Ranjith Kumar Divyansh Baranwal",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:08:52.355Z"),
    "question" : "What is the scope of a chartered accountant in the business analyst career in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 5 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60364ff50c817f0398fa5aac"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-possible-to-start-a-career-as-a-business-analyst-after-a-non-tech-job?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Is it possible to start a career as a business analyst after a non-tech job?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:09:09.041Z"),
    "question" : "Is it possible to start a career as a business analyst after a non-tech job? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 6 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036501a0c817f0398fa5b02"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Should-I-switch-my-career-from-software-developer-to-Business-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:09:46.986Z"),
    "question" : "Should I switch my career from software developer to Business analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 7 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036502b0c817f0398fa5b18"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-CRM-tool-is-better-between-Salesforce-and-MS-Dynamics-for-a-Techno-Functional-Business-analyst-career-growth-prospective?-",
    "answer" : "The answer depends on your target. What company do you have in mind and what system is used there? Some large companies also use Oracle, Netsuite and SAP CRM, so you might also want to consider those other CRM tools. I guess the main considerations in choosing between Dynamics and Salesforce for your career would be these: Your previous experience. It’s easier to build on the knowledge you already have than start from a clean slate. If you’ve got C# and .Net code experience, then it’s easier to transition to MS Dynamics. For Salesforce, you need to be familiar with Apex and Java.The type of organization you want to work for. Dynamics and Salesforce appeal to different kinds of organizations. B2B companies seem to like Salesforce more, while software companies prefer Dynamics.Your preferred deployment. Both Microsoft and Salesforce have CRM in the cloud. Dynamics 365 is a cloud-first product while the SF sales, marketing and service clouds (which comprise the usual CRM system) have always been deployed via the cloud. Microsoft, though, still provides on-premise Dynamics software for companies that prefer legacy systems.If you want to broaden your options and get more opportunities, then maybe you can try learning both the SF CRM and MS Dynamics. Be aware, though, that these two CRM systems are very different from each other. It would take a lot of effort to learn both so be prepared to dedicate a lot of time to such an ambitious project.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:10:03.361Z"),
    "question" : "Which CRM tool is better between Salesforce and MS Dynamics for a Techno-Functional Business analyst career growth prospective? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 8 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036503c0c817f0398fa5b62"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-steps-to-building-a-career-as-a-business-technology-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:10:20.401Z"),
    "question" : "What are the steps to building a career as a business technology analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 9 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603650880c817f0398fa5bd8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-mandatory-to-study-for-an-MBA-for-taking-a-business-analyst-as-a-career?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Abhishek Dwivedi Yogesh Kaushik",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:11:36.020Z"),
    "question" : "Is it mandatory to study for an MBA for taking a business analyst as a career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 10 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603650c20c817f0398fa5c44"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-a-business-analyst-become-a-scrum-master?-Or-will-it-hinder-his/her-career-growth-in-future?-",
    "answer" : "Why not? If she is an excellent coach and good at Scrum methodology she can be a good Scrummaster as well as a good Business Analyst. But more likely, a good Product Owner. If she is good at saying “No”. A Business Analyst is good at defining a Vision into Goals and transforming them into demands and User Stories, evaluate Value and Effort with the Team and the Stakeholders. Just as the Product Owner. Jim Pruitt",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:12:34.670Z"),
    "question" : "Can a business analyst be a good scrum master? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 11 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603651470c817f0398fa5d20"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-change-my-career-path-from-being-a-software-developer-to-a-business-analyst-in-Australia?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers How do I change my career path from being a software developer to a business analyst in Australia? Hello there. Firstly I've been in the same boat as you, worked as a developer for the first 3 years of my career and recently moved into a business analyst role. This is what helped me land the interview and ace it! The first part is landing the interview, you would want to tweak your CV a little to better suit the position you're applying for. This does not mean you must lie, it's never a good idea to lie on your CV instead try to add more focus on the tasks you did that involved business analysis, also focus on your skills make sure you highlight all transferable skills such as problem solving, logical thinking, data analysis, these are skills that are used across the board in system development and design and are often key skills in business analysis. The second thing you need to do is  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:14:47.129Z"),
    "question" : "How do I change my career path from being a software developer to a business analyst in Australia? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 12 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036516c0c817f0398fa5d82"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-should-be-my-career-path-if-I-want-to-become-business-analyst-in-an-investment-bank?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the Business analyst role in payments domain?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:15:24.049Z"),
    "question" : "What should be my career path if I want to become business analyst in an investment bank? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036519e0c817f0398fa5de4"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-working-from-a-data-scientist-to-a-business-intelligence-analyst-considered-a-downgrade-in-your-career-ladder?-",
    "answer" : "Not really! It depends on what are the responsibilities and the things that you do in each role, especially where the title “Data scientist” and “Business intelligent analyst” is usually being over used and poor defined in many different countries, companies. So it really depend on the context you are in to say more about it. Does the environment/market you are in have well developed labour market of the “DATA” field?Is this a move within a company or from one to another?How different is data scientist role compare to the business intelligence analyst?I am in Vietnam, where I saw companies hiring data scientist who has PhD, in mathematics, very strong background in machine learning but have little knowledge of how to fit that knowledge into business and the use of his work to the company was limited. In fact, he was perform very much like a BI analyst with a bit extra machine learning, however, due to limited in domain knowledge his output was far less comprehensive and insightful compare to a BI analyst with lower level of education. Finally, the business problems you are able to solve with using the knowledge, data & technology you have at hand that make different not the job title. How much impact is the matter to your career more than a mere title.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:16:14.481Z"),
    "question" : "Is working from a data scientist to a business intelligence analyst considered a downgrade in your career ladder? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 14 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603651b60c817f0398fa5df8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-future-of-business-analysts?-In-India-if-I-start-my-business-analyst-career-now,-what-will-be-my-future-10-15-years-down-the-road?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the scope of business analysts in the near future?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:16:38.902Z"),
    "question" : "What is the scope of business analysts in the near future? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 15 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603652130c817f0398fa5eb8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-change-my-career-from-an-CPA-Accountant-to-a-Business-Analyst?-",
    "answer" : "James Lancaster, Former Job HunterAnswered 7 years ago · Author has 195 answers and 550K answer viewsHow can I change my career from an CPA Accountant to a Business Analyst? James Lancaster It may be an easier change than you think. Business Analysis is such a wide field that anyone with any analytical inclination can join.  Given the similarities between skill sets, you may not even need to make an industry/organisation jump.  Your existing work experience may be attractive to employers looking for analysts with proven industry knowledge. Your time as a CPA qualified accountant is likely to have given you numerous and valuable transferable skills [1]: Conceptual Modelling Skills Communicating Details and Concepts CuriosityDecomposing the Abstract into Details Mentoring and Coaching Communicating RisksChange Management Asking why? You may well be already qualified for a Business Analyst job. Check out your own CPA website for more details on where your CPA accreditation can tak Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:18:11.912Z"),
    "question" : "How can I change my career from an CPA Accountant to a Business Analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 16 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603652520c817f0398fa5f27"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-a-business-analyst-a-good-career-or-digital-marketing?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Is a business analyst a good career or digital marketing?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:19:14.551Z"),
    "question" : "Is a business analyst a good career or digital marketing? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 17 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603652800c817f0398fa5f55"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-become-a-data-scientist-as-Physics-PhD?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Tianqi Chen",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T13:20:00.281Z"),
    "question" : "How do I become a data scientist as Physics PhD? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}